<?xml version="1.0"?>
<addon scheme="2.0">
	<id>advanced_addon</id>
	<name>Advanced Add-on</name>
	<description>Advanced Add-on</description>
	<version>1.0</version>
	<priority>100500</priority>
	<status>active</status>  
	<queries>
        <item for="install">DROP TABLE IF EXISTS ?:label_value;</item>

		<item for="install">DROP TABLE IF EXISTS ?:video_document;</item>

		<item for="install">
            CREATE TABLE `?:label_value` (
				`id` int(11) unsigned NOT NULL AUTO_INCREMENT,
				`tab_name` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				`label_name` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				`label_details` text NULL DEFAULT '',
				PRIMARY KEY (`id`)
			) Engine=MyISAM DEFAULT CHARSET UTF8;
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			CREATE TABLE `?:video_document` (
				`id` int(11) unsigned NOT NULL AUTO_INCREMENT,
				`parent_name` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				`tab_name` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				`upload_type` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				`url` varchar(255) NULL DEFAULT '',
				PRIMARY KEY (`id`)
			) Engine=MyISAM DEFAULT CHARSET UTF8;
		</item>

        <item for="install">
            INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'General', 'Name', 'Enter the name of the product as you’d like it to appear on the mall.'), ('', 'General', 'Categories', 'Begin typing a category that you’d like the product to be listed under. Then select the proper category for the product. 
'), ('', 'General', 'Price', 'Enter the product price in US Dollars.'), ('', 'General', 'Full description', 'Enter a description of the product which will appear on the product details page. You can either use plain text or a formatted HTML text.'), ('', 'General', 'Status', 'Select the status of the product: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Active—the product is available on the mall and appears in the product list.</li><li>Disabled—the product is not available on the mall.</li><li>Hidden—the product does not appear in the product list on the mall. Customers can reach a hidden product via a direct link.</li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'Images', 'Drag and drop or select images of the product from your computer the images. Supported formats include JPEG, GIF, and PNG. The maximum size of an uploaded image is 2-MB.'), ('', 'General', 'Options type', 'Select how the options and variants of this product appear and work on the mall: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Simultaneous – Allow your customers to choose the variant for each option independently and in any order. </li><li>Sequential – Options and variants are chosen one after another: first the variant of the first option, then the variant of the second option, and so on. </li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'Exceptions type', 'select a type of the product option exceptions: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Forbidden—you’ll be able to specify Forbidden combinations on the Options tab. Customers won’t be able to purchase a product when they choose a forbidden combination of option variants.</li><li>Allowed—you’ll be able to specify Allowed combinations on the Options tab. Customers will only be able to select these combinations of option variants.</li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'CODE', 'Enter the identifier of the product that you use in your store (a stock keeping unit or SKU).'), ('', 'General', 'List price', 'Enter the list price of the product. If the price entered is higher than the product’s Price, a discount label will be displayed for the product.'), ('', 'General', 'In stock', 'Enter the number of products in the stock.'), ('', 'General', 'Zero price action', 'Determines what can be done on the mall when the product’s Price is 0: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Do not allow customers to add the product to cart</li><li>Allow customers to add the product to cart</li><li>Ask customers to enter the price — Customers will see an input field and will be able to enter the price that they are willing to pay. This is useful for charity events or donations.</li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'Track Inventory', 'Enter how you would like WeSave to handle tracking of inventory of this product: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Yes - When inventory is tracked, the number of products in stock will decrease after each purchase. </li><li>No – WeSave will not track your inventory, therefore, the number of products in stock will stay the same after each purchase.</li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'Minimum quantity to buy per product', 'Enter the minimum number of items that a customer can buy at a time. This number will appear on the product page on the mall, right after the product price.'), ('', 'General', 'Maximum order quantity', 'Enter the maximum number of items that a customer can buy at a time. 0 means no limit.'), ('', 'General', 'Quantity step', 'Enter the quantity step by which a customer can increase or decrease the number of the product in cart.'), ('', 'General', 'Number of available quantities', 'the maximum number of choices in the Quantity drop-down list. It comes useful when you set a quantity step and when there are a lot of items in stock.'), ('', 'General', 'Taxes', 'if you tick the checkbox, it will be assumed that you specified the prices of products with tax included. Otherwise, the tax will be added to the order subtotal when a customer places an order'), ('', 'General', 'User groups', 'Select the user groups that can access the product’s page.'), ('', 'General', 'Creation date', 'Enter the date when the product was adding to the catalog.'), ('', 'General', 'Avail since', 'Enter the date when the product becomes available for purchase. It is useful when you want to start selling at a specific date, or when the product isn’t available yet.'), ('', 'General', 'Out of stock actions', 'Select the options available to the customers if the product is out of stock. <![CDATA[<ul><li>None—forbid customers from buying the product in one of the following cases: <ul><li>When the product is out of stock.</li><li>If you have specified a future date when the product would become available (the Avail since property of a product).</li></ul></li><li>Buy in advance—make the product available on backorder; customers will be able to order this product, regardless of the availability date and whether or not the product is in stock. </li><li>Sign up for notification—offer customers to sign up for an email notification so that they receive an email once the product is in stock again.</li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'General', 'Product details view', 'Choose a template (basically, the look) of the product page. Currently, there are 4 templates available.'), ('', 'General', 'Short description', 'Write a short product description; it appears on the product list on your mall. If you leave this field blank, the short description will be automatically taken from the full product description (first 300 characters).'), ('', 'General', 'Popularity', 'This rating depends on the number of product views as well as the number of times the product was added to the cart and purchased. Products can be sorted by popularity on the storefront.'), ('', 'General', 'Search words', 'Enter the list of words (separated by a comma) by which the product should be easily found by the built-in search engine.'), ('', 'General', 'Promo text', 'Enter additional information that appears on the top right side of the product page.');
        </item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'SEO', 'SEO name', 'If you desire you can change the product name in the default product URL (eg. http://store.wesave.com/toys/childrens-toys/barbie210510)'), ('', 'SEO', 'Page title', 'Enter the content of the <![CDATA[<title></title>]]> container: the title of the product page on the storefront, which is displayed in the web browser when somebody is viewing the page. If you don’t specify a page title, it will be generated automatically.'), ('', 'SEO', 'META description', 'Enter a brief description of the product for the content of the meta-tag.'), ('', 'SEO', 'META keywords', 'Enter a list of search keywords that appear on the product page.'), ('', 'SEO', 'Google rich snippets preview', 'This is a preview of how Google will display your search results. <![CDATA[<ul><li>What are Rich Snippets? - Rich Snippets (also known as “Rich Results”) are normal Google search results with additional data displayed. This extra data is usually pulled from Structured Data found in a page’s HTML. Common Rich Snippet types include reviews, recipes and events. </li></ul>]]>');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Options', 'Options type', 'Select how the options and variants of this product appear and work on the storefront: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Simultaneous—customers can choose the variant for each option independently and in any order.</li><li>Sequential—options and variants are chosen one after another: first the variant of the first option, then the variant of the second option, and so on. </li></ul>]]> Options are specific properties of the product that a customer can choose when making a purchase. For example, options for clothes may include color and size. The variants of those options would be red/green/blue and S/M/L/XL/XXL respectively.'), ('', 'Options', 'Exceptions type', 'select a type of the product option exceptions: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Forbidden—you’ll be able to specify Forbidden combinations on the Options tab. Customers won’t be able to purchase a product when they choose a forbidden combination of option variants.</li><li>Allowed—you’ll be able to specify Allowed combinations on the Options tab. Customers will only be able to select these combinations of option variants.</li></ul>]]>');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Options', 'Options type', 'Select how the options and variants of this product appear and work on the storefront: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Simultaneous—customers can choose the variant for each option independently and in any order.</li><li>Sequential—options and variants are chosen one after another: first the variant of the first option, then the variant of the second option, and so on. </li></ul>]]> Options are specific properties of the product that a customer can choose when making a purchase. For example, options for clothes may include color and size. The variants of those options would be red/green/blue and S/M/L/XL/XXL respectively.'), ('', 'Options', 'Exceptions type', 'select a type of the product option exceptions: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Forbidden—you’ll be able to specify Forbidden combinations on the Options tab. Customers won’t be able to purchase a product when they choose a forbidden combination of option variants.</li><li>Allowed—you’ll be able to specify Allowed combinations on the Options tab. Customers will only be able to select these combinations of option variants.</li></ul>]]>');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Variations', 'Click Add Variations', 'You can Click Add All Variants to add all available variants and then “Deselect” the variant that are not available. You can also add individual variants');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Weight', 'Enter the weight of a single item in the store’s default weight measurement unit.'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Free shipping', 'If you tick this checkbox, the product will be excluded from the shipping cost calculation'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Shipping freight', 'Enter any handling fee (insurance, packaging, etc.) to be added to the shipping cost.'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Items in a box', 'Enter the minimum and maximum number of product items to be shipped in a separate box. Usually it’s 1 - 1 (only one product per box).'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Box length', 'Enter the minimum and maximum number of product items to be shipped in a separate box. Usually it’s 1 - 1 (only one product per box).'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Box length', 'Enter the length of the shipping box.'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Box width', 'Enter the width of the shipping box.'), ('', 'Shipping properties', 'Box height', 'Enter the height of the shipping box.');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Quantity', 'Enter the minimum number of product items to qualify for the product alternative price.'), ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Value', 'the value of the discount (per item).'), ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Type', 'the type of the discount: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Absolute—the cost of 1 discounted item.</li><li>Percent—the percent discount off the base product item price. </li></ul>]]>');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Quantity', 'Enter the minimum number of product items to qualify for the product alternative price.'), ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Value', 'the value of the discount (per item).'), ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'Type', 'the type of the discount: <![CDATA[<ul><li>Absolute—the cost of 1 discounted item.</li><li>Percent—the percent discount off the base product item price. </li></ul>]]>'), ('', 'Quantity discounts', 'User group', 'Enter the user group which can take advantage of the discounted price. Note: If you set up a discount that applies for all user groups for purchasing 1 item, this will overwrite product price.');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Add-ons', 'Returnable', 'Tick this checkbox for the product will be labeled as returnable.'), ('', 'Add-ons', 'Return period', 'Enter the time period (in days) during which the product can be returned. The period begins on the day of purchase.'), ('', 'Add-ons', 'Sales amount', 'the number of sold product items. This value is calculated automatically. However, you can change the current value manually.'), ('', 'Add-ons', 'Comments and reviews', '<![CDATA[<ul><li>Communication and Rating—customers can write a review and rate the object on the scale from 1 to 5.</li> <li>Communication—customers can write a review but can’t rate the object. </li> <li>Rating—customers can rate the object, but can’t write a review.</li> <li>Disabled—customers can’t write a review or rate the object.</li></ul>]]>');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Features', 'Returnable', 'Tick this checkbox for the product will be labeled as returnable.'), ('', 'Features', 'Color', 'Select the primary color of the product.  Customers will be able to select the desired color on the product page'), ('', 'Features', 'Size', 'Select the primary Size of the product.  Customers will be able to select the desired size on the product page');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Buy together', 'Name', 'Enter the name of the product combination.'), ('', 'Buy together', 'Description', 'Enter the description of the product combination as it appears on the storefront.'), ('', 'Buy together', 'Available from', 'Enter the date when the product combination becomes available for customers. '), ('', 'Buy together', 'Available till', 'Enter the date until the product combination is available.'), ('', 'Buy together', 'Display in promotions', 'if this checkbox is ticked, the combination will appear on the list of promotions.'), ('', 'Buy together', 'Status', 'the status of the product combination (Active or Disabled).');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Store Pickup', 'Enable Store Pickup', 'Check this box if store pick up is offered.'), ('', 'Store Pickup', 'Strict Store Pickup mode', 'Check this box if the item must be picked up at the store'), ('', 'Store Pickup', 'Strict Store Pickup mode', 'Add a pickup location including the inventory at that store Select Store Pickup location and enter the quantity in stock in each location');
		</item>

		<item for="install">
			INSERT INTO `?:label_value` (`id`, `tab_name`, `label_name`, `label_details`) VALUES ('', 'Digitzs', 'first_name', 'The merchant’s first_name.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'last_name', 'The merchant’s last name.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_email', 'The merchant`s email address.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'day_phone', 'The merchant’s daytime contact number.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'evening_phone', 'The merchant’s evening contact number.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'birth_date', 'The merchant’s date of birth.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'social_security', 'The merchant’s social security number.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_address_line1', 'A key for grouping personal address information.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_city', 'The city where the individual is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_country', 'The three-character country code.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_country', 'The three-character country code.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_state', 'The state where the individual is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'personal_zip', 'The postal code where the individual is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'same_as_above', 'A key for grouping personal address information.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'same_as_above', 'A key for grouping personal address information.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_name', 'The legal name of the business as registered.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'url', ''), ('', 'Digitzs', 'ein', 'The Employer Identification Number (EIN).'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_address_line1', 'A key for grouping business address information.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_city', 'The city where the business is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_country', 'The three-character country code.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_state', 'The state where the business is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'business_zipcode', 'The postal code where the business is located.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'bank_name', 'The name of the financial institution.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_ownership', 'The valid values are Personal or Business.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_type', 'The type of bank account (Checking or Savings).'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_type', 'The type of bank account (Checking or Savings).'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_name', 'The first and last name of the account holder.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_number', 'The financial institution account number. It is required if boarding with the primary bank on file.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'account_number', 'The financial institution account number. It is required if boarding with the primary bank on file.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'routing_number', 'The bank routing number. This is required if the payment method is checking or savings.'), ('', 'Digitzs', 'merchant_agreement', '');
		</item>

        <item for="uninstall">DROP TABLE IF EXISTS ?:label_value;</item>
		<item for="uninstall">DROP TABLE IF EXISTS ?:video_document;</item>
	</queries>
</addon>